Guide to the Furioso Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Submissions, 1937-51; Series II; 1.67; (4 boxes)
  - ZATURENSKA, MARYA
    - "House of Chimeras", n.d.
    - "The Listening Landscape"
    - "Quiet Countries: Or the World of Hans Christian Anderson"
    - "Final Stanza of Quiet Countries Should Read" (Correction of previous), n.d.
    - "Tears and Thistles"
  - UNIDENTIFIED
    - Unsigned "Bulletins" for the "Department of Culture" column, [1949-51] (Box 6, Folder 337-341)
    - Unsigned, untitled essay concerning Van Wyck Brooks: autograph and typescript (Box 6, Folder 342-343)
    - Unsigned poems, [1949-50], n.d. (Box 6, Folder 344)
- Office Files, 1939-51; Series III; 2.09; (5 boxes)
  Series III, Office Files. is divided into four alphabetically arranged subseries: Advertising and Promotion Files, Editorial Board Files, Printing and Distribution Files, and Subscription Files. Material within each series is arranged alphabetically by type.
  - ADVERTISING AND PROMOTION FILES
    - Advertising
      - Correspondence with magazines concerning ad exchanges, A-Z, 1947-50 (Box 7, Folder 345-351)
      - Placements in Furioso, 1947-49 (Box 7, Folder 352-354)
    - Promotion
      - Correspondence, A-Z, 1946-49 (Box 7, Folder 355)
      - "Examples and Ideas", 1947, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 356-357)
      - Promotional material, 1939-51, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 358-359)
      - "Publicity -- Clippings", 1947 (Box 7, Folder 360)
      - Scrapbook, 1939-40 (Box 7, Folder 360a)
  - EDITORIAL BOARD FILES
    - Correspondence
      - Intra-board correspondence, 1946-49 (Box 8, Folder 361-374)
        Correspondents include: Howard Nemerov, Reed Whittemore, Rosemary Mizener.
      - Publishers' correspondence, A-Z, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 375-382)
        Concerning the Poetry Book Club.
      - Review copy requests, 1947-48 (Box 9, Folder 383-384)
    - "Issue Files"
      - Early issues, [ca. 1939-41] (Box 9, Folder 385)
      - "Winter, 1947", 1947, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 386)
      - "Spring, 1948", 1948, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 387)
      - "Summer, 1948", 1948, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 388)
      - "1949", 1949, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 389)
      - "Winter, 1949", 1949, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 390)
      - "Spring, 1949", 1949, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 391)
      - "Summer, 1949", 1949, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 392)
      - "Fall, 1949", 1949, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 393)
      - "Winter, 1950", 1949, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 394)
      - "Spring, 1950", 1949-50, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 395)
      - "Summer, 1950", 1950, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 396)
      - "Fall, 1950", 1950, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 397)
      - "Winter, 1951", 1951, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 398-399)
      - "Spring, 1951", 1951, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 400-401)
      - "Ideas left over", 1947-48, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 402)
    - Other Board Files
      - Artwork, 1949-50 (Box 10, Folder 403-404)
      - "Expenses, misc.", 1947-49 (Box 10, Folder 405)
      - "Furioso Stationery", n.d. (Box 10, Folder 406)
      - Lists of contributors, 1947-49 (Box 10, Folder 407)
      - Lists, miscellaneous, 1947, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 408)
      - Printed material, 1947-50 (Box 10, Folder 409)
  - PRINTING AND DISTRIBUTION FILES
    - Printing
      - Columbia Printing Company, 1946-48 (Box 11, Folder 410)
    - Distribution
      - Arrangements with bookstores, 1947-48 (Box 11, Folder 411)
      - Arrangements with distributors, 1949-50 (Box 11, Folder 412)
  - SUBSCRIPTIONS FILES
    - Correspondence
      - Individual subscriptions, A-Z, 1946-48 (Box 11, Folder 413-414)
      - Institutional subscriptions, A-Z, 1947-49 (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Other Files
      - Account books, 1939-48 (Box 11, Folder 416-417)
      - Invoices, 1947-50 (Box 11, Folder 418-419)
      - Lists of subscribers, 1940-49, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 420-421)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 1.76; (2 boxes)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Boxes 12-13: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 7 and folder 14 (Box 12, Folder 422)
  - Box 1, folder 21 and folder 23 (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - Box 1, folder 25 (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Box 1, folder 26 (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - Box 1, folder 33 (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Box 1, folder 44 and folder 57 (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Box 1, folder 59 (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Box 1, folder 65 (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - Box 2, folder 67 (Box 12, Folder 430)
  - Box 2, folder 69 (Box 12, Folder 431)
  - Box 2, folder 85 (Box 12, Folder 432)
  - Box 2, folder 98 (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Box 2, folder 113 (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - Box 2, folder 124 (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - Box 2, folder 127 (Box 12, Folder 436)
  - Box 2, folder 132 (Box 12, Folder 437)
  - Box 3, folder 146 (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Box 3, folder 153 (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - Box 3, folder 173 (Box 12, Folder 440)
  - Box 3, folder 179 (Box 12, Folder 441)
  - Box 3, folder 192 (Box 12, Folder 442)
  - Box 4, folder 196 (Box 12, Folder 443)
  - Box 4, folder 198 (Box 12, Folder 444)
  - Box 4, folder 210 (Box 12, Folder 445)
  - Box 4, folder 233 (Box 12, Folder 446)
  - Box 4, folder 234 (Box 12, Folder 447)
  - Box 5, folder 249 (Box 12, Folder 448)
  - Box 5, folder 274 (Box 12, Folder 449)
  - Box 5, folder 277 (Box 12, Folder 450)
  - Box 5, folder 279 (Box 12, Folder 451)
  - Box 5, folder 282 (Box 12, Folder 452)
  - Box 6, folder 299 (Box 12, Folder 453)
  - Box 6, folder 310 (Box 12, Folder 454)
  - Box 6, folder 336 (Box 12, Folder 455)
  - Box 7, folders 345-351 (Box 12, Folder 456-463)
  - Box 7, folder 355 (Box 12, Folder 464)
  - Box 7, folder 357 (Box 12, Folder 465)
  - Box 7, folder 358 (Box 12, Folder 466)
  - Box 7, folder 360 (Box 12, Folder 466a)
  - Box 8, folders 361-374 (Box 12, Folder 467-468)
  - Box 9, folder 383-384 (Box 12, Folder 469)
  - Box 9, folder 387 (Box 12, Folder 470)
  - Box 9, folder 388 (Box 12, Folder 471)
  - Box 9, folder 389 (Box 12, Folder 472)
  - Box 9, folder 396 (Box 12, Folder 472a)
  - Box 9, folder 400 (Box 12, Folder 472b)
  - Box 9, folder 402 (Box 12, Folder 473)
  - Box 9, folder 405 (Box 12, Folder 474)
  - Box 9, folder 407 (Box 12, Folder 475)
  - Box 9, folder 408 (Box 12, Folder 476)
  - Box 9, folder 409 (Box 12, Folder 477)
  - Box 11, folder 410 (Box 12, Folder 478)
  - Box 11, folder 414 (Box 12, Folder 479)
  - Box 11, folder 415 (Box 12, Folder 480)
  - Box 7, folder 360a (Box 13, Folder 481)
- Oversize, 0.67; (1 box)
  - Downer, Alan S. Fragment of a drama review proof (in Series II), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 482)
  - Spring, 1949, galley proof (in Series III), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 483)
  - Summer, 1949, galley proof (in Series III), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 484)
  - Fall, 1949, galley proof (in Series III), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 485)
  - Spring, 1950, galley proof (in Series III), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 486)
  - Summer, 1950, galley proof (in Series III), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 487)
  - Fall, 1950, galley proof (in Series III), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 488)
  - Spring, 1951, galley proof (in Series III), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 489)
  - Artwork (in Series III), n.d. (Box Port, folder 490)